http://www.angelmatcher.com/privacy_policy

Skip to main content
HomeAbout UsCycling / Transfers / DeliveriesIntended Parent Surrogate/Donor InformationLinksAvailable Egg DonorsHIV & SurrogacySurrogacy ApplicationCelebrating 20!
ServicesContact InformationPrivacy PolicyIn Loving MemoryTraditional Surrogacy
Acupuncture & FertilityProjected Surrogacy CostsPayment Options**Adoption Information**References/TestimonialsFinancing NOW available!
Surrogacy ApplicationSurrogate/Donor Info RequestTraditional Surrogacy - AI InformationBody Mass Index ChartAttention Experienced Surrogates
Surrogacy LinksReproductive Medicine LinksGay/Lesbian LinksAttorney ReferralsOther Links
Privacy Policy
AngelMatcher Privacy Policy
I promise not to disclose your private information to any third party except if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of AngelMatcher users or the public. I take all reasonable care in handling your personal information to ensure its security both offline and online.
Types of Information I CollectYou are free to browse AngelMatcher.com without submitting any personal information at all. Your IP address (your current Internet address) is stored in the server logs at the time of your visit, as it is on all web sites. I do not collect any personal information (such as a name, address or e-mail address) when you visit the site unless you register for the message board or mailing list.
Message Board RegistrationYou may read the message boards without registering, but you must register to post. You must provide a real email address (not a free web-based email address) when you register. You can configure the board not to display your email address to other users.
CookiesThe message boards use browser cookies to keep track of which messages you have read, your login, and other information about your session. Cookies are small pieces of text that are stored on your hard drive between visits. For example, I use a cookie to store your username and password so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain any private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept these cookies to visit or use the site (although turning cookies off will severely impair the board's functionality), and you can choose to refuse the cookies, delete the cookies from your hard drive or turn off cookies at any time by updating your user profile preferences.
Postings on Message BoardsIt is important remember that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a online posting that that information is visible to anyone, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, I discourage you from posting any personal information on this or any message board.
Home About Us Cycling / Transfers / Deliveries Intended Parent
Surrogate/Donor Information Links Available Egg Donors HIV & Surrogacy Surrogacy Application Celebrating 20!
Site Mailing List
Matching Angels... Making Miracles....
Now with 2 offices to proudly serve you!
